<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The 0 Among 1s</title>
    <link>https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>The 0 Among 1s (Posts)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 22:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Write!</title>
      <link>https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/justwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 22:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/justwrite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Just Write&lt;/u&gt;
We&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to the first official post and we&amp;rsquo;re at a roadblock. I just have too much to write about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem that I&amp;rsquo;ve had time and time again with this blog is that I find myself being lost for words because I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to talk about first. I come up with idea after idea with what I can say and honestly, I just get too caught up in what should be the best and didn&amp;rsquo;t take a moment to just write. This is meant to be a personal log of my thoughts, emotions, and experiences in the field and throughout life. There&amp;rsquo;s no correct or incorrect way to portray thoughts unless they&amp;rsquo;re not the actual thoughts themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of this blog&amp;rsquo;s direction has moved from place to place and I&amp;rsquo;ve come to the understanding that this is something to nurture and to grow. It could be an expression of feelings of imperfection or injustice or, it could be advice on how I overcame hardships and the experiences around them. At the moment, the concept is that you (the reader) would have to either go on to my social media profile or scan my business card and then read the thoughts that have run across my mind. If you don&amp;rsquo;t like what I have to say that&amp;rsquo;s okay. But it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be something to hold against my character or make an attempt to demean or &amp;ldquo;Make fun of&amp;rdquo; me because this may just not be meant for you and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, at the time of writing this, I&amp;rsquo;m currently balancing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A social Life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A university degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General life things
This (as can be assumed) is quite a balancing act and this could mean that there&amp;rsquo;s (unintentionally) little consistency with posting but I&amp;rsquo;ll just try to make time where I can.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But enough of the complaining. At the moment I&amp;rsquo;m working on posts with the titles:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Greener Grasses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Imposter Syndrome&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Progression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pathways&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crossroads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Envy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, I&amp;rsquo;ve got some big ambitions and I hope that you follow my journey. Also, feel free to contact me either via email at &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@taylorwatson.co.uk&#34;&gt;contact@taylorwatson.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; (or you can click the email icon in the top right, or message me on LinkedIn because I&amp;rsquo;d love to answer any questions you have or to just have a chat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 21:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taylorwatson.co.uk/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This could be a welcome back for some of you or the first hello from me with this blog.
I initially started this back in 2019 when I started my first apprenticeship but I had a lot to deal with which I&amp;rsquo;ve now been able to get more of a handle on and I&amp;rsquo;m now jumping back onto the wagon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the point?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog will contain primarily my thoughts and a point of view from a fairly new member of the STEM/InfoSec/CyberSecurity industry and hopefully provide you with a new angle to the field. If you have any questions please feel free to contact me at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@taylorwatson.co.uk&#34;&gt;contact@taylorwatson.co.uk&lt;/a&gt; or just drop me a message on my LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to keep this consistent but please bear in mind that I&amp;rsquo;m juggling a full-time degree, working and progressing in a SOC (Security Operations Center), and then also trying to balance my life as a (current) teenager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also note that the format of this site may change as time goes on and that&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to find out what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than that. Thank you for reading, I hope you find this interesting, and I hope that you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to stick around for the journey which is my career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
